

Contact

Phone

+94-76-840-7950

Email

tharun.varshanth.k@gmail.com

Address

No 02, Haputale Road, Diyathalawa,

SriLanka

Linkdin

TharunVarshanth Krishnamoorthy

Githuh

Tharunvarshanth

Programming Languages

Java

JavaScript

• Go

TypeScript

 Python • SQL

Dart

• C

Databases

- MySQL
- Mongo
- PostgreSQL

Tharun Varshanth Krishnamoorthy

Software Engineer at Daraz

As a highly skilled and experienced software engineer and full-stack developer, bring strong background in web and mobile to the table. I am confident that my dedication to the experience, and commitment to fostering an engaging learning environment align with the requirements of this position. I am confident that my qualifications and enthusiasm make me an excellent candidate for this role

Education

B.SC(Hons) in Software Engineering

2019 Feb - 2023 June University of Kelaniya | GPA 3.54

Cambridge ESOL Entry Level Certificate

ESOL International Entry 1

2013 | Result : Council of Europe Level A1

Bandarawela Education Centre Computer Unit

2018 | Advanced Diploma In Computer Hardware

Results: B+

S.Thomas College, Bandarawela

2017 A/L | physical science stream

Results: 3B

Work Experience

2023 March (Present)

Daraz Financial Services Software Engineer

1. KOKO

• Users can shop at their favorite retailers just got easier with a Python-based Decision engine system. They can split the cost of their purchases into 3 interest-free payments.

Vue js | Spring Boot | Mysql | Alibaba cloud | FastApi | **Android**

2. Daraz Seller Credit

• Giving the loan to the daraz sellers through sellers site Spring Boot (Pandora Boot) | Vue js

2021 Aug - 2023 March

Mitra Innovations

Associate Software Engineer

1. Sillara Agri Tech

• Sillara is an online market place located in SriLanka connecting B2B. Hotel, and restaurants can directly connect vegetable and grocery suppliers.

AWS | Cognito | React | aws serverless lambda .NET

2. Dygisec Triton

 Headquartered in Singapore, with operations in SriLanka and the US, Dygisec product company focused on Cloud Security. DygiSec is Cloud agentless, data driven cloud security solution

AWS | GO | Angular | Keycloak | Microservice | ngrx | Kong | Docker | Kubernetes

Intern Software Engineer

1. Cellcard Mobile

Cambodian Telecoms company operating in 4G LTE.
Selfcare Mobile app available on android, ios, huawei android platforms. I worked on react native and android, ios huawei native level configurations.

React Native | aws server less lambda-node js | Bitrise

Volunteer Experience

RealHack 4.0 | Software Engineering Students Association
2022 - 2023 | Organizing Committee

• Former Studpro 4.0 | IEEE SL Young Professionals 2021 - 2020 | Web Editor

Achievements

OGoogle Hashcode Participation | 2021

Azure Cloud Skill Challenges Top 20 | 2021

Arimac Future Cast IOT Ideathon | 2021

Certification Courses

PEdx

2020-Present

Applied Scrum for Agile Project Management AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials

Alison

2020 - 2021

Operating Systems Courses

Diploma in Design Thinking

Scrum Immersion

Referee

Deleema Fernando

Senior Tech Lead at Lucytec

E-mail: deleemarf@gmail.com Mobile: +94-71-552-6825

Frameworks & Technologies

- Spring boot
- React js

Angular

- Vue Js
- Flutter
- Firebase
- Express Js
- Android
- Docker
- AWS
- React Native (
- los
- Git
- Kubernetes

Soft Skills

- Team Player
- Communication
- Problem Solver
- Time Management

Interest

- Playing Cricket
- Traveling
- Volunteer Work
- Technology Blogging
- Continuous Learning
- Mentoring